殺してやる
I'll kill you...
よくも　みんなを…
for what you did to them!
その意気だ　殺しに来なさい
That's the spirit!
Come and kill me,
渚君
Nagisa-kun!
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
起立
礼
ロックオン
起立
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
礼
ロックオン
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
せんせー
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
ターゲットオン
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
ポテンシャル高い
We've got a lot of potential
potential takai
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
ポテンシャル高い
ほどめんどくさい
It's just that we're not trying
hodo mendokusai
ほどめんどくさい
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
ほどめんどくさい
ドロップアウト　メンタリティー
We had that dropouts' mentality
dropout mentality
ほどめんどくさい
ドロップアウト　メンタリティー
翻译.兰樱
非日常を凌駕し
No matter the unusual situation we were in
hinichijou wo ryougashi
非日常を凌駕し
翻译.兰樱
校对.Maki
非日常を凌駕し
We pretended to doze off
bokura wa utatanegao shite
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
僕らはうたたね顔して
While holding on to a hidden knife
knife kakushimotta
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
ナイフ隠し持った
起立
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
礼
ロックオン
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
ほっとけば　きっと誰か　やってくれると
どこか　他人事だった
We didn't really feel invested in the job
doko ka taningoto datta
どこか　他人事だった
だけど
But now
dakedo
だけど
Mr.ティーチャー教えて　未完成の僕ら
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
あなたという不落のターゲット　撃抜けるでしょうか
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
あなたという不落のターゲット　撃抜けるでしょうか
挑む限り　可能性はハーフ＆ハーフ
As long as we challenge you, it's fifty-fifty
Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu kagiri kanousei wa half and half
kiritsu rei lock on
挑む限り　可能性はハーフ＆ハーフ
Mr.ティーチャー見ていて　迷い多き僕ら
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
誰よりもあなたのために猛勉強中さ
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
誰よりもあなたのために猛勉強中さ
殺意だけが　あなたへのメッセージ
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
satsui dake ga anata e no message
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
殺意だけが　あなたへのメッセージ
自力　ガチで
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
自力　ガチで
本願　行くよ
A revolution!
revolution
レボリューション
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
せんせー
ターゲットオン
Episode
Nagisa
Time
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 i.kamigami.org 及微博 @诸神字幕组
渚　キレてる
Nagisa...
snapped!
俺らだって殺してえよ　あのごみ野郎
Sure, we'd all like to kill that rotten son of a bitch.
けど　渚のやつ　マジでやる気か
but Nagisa might just go through with it!
いけない　渚君を止め…
No! You have to stop—
調子こいてんじゃねえぞ　渚
Don't be gettin' cocky, Nagisa!
薬が爆破されたときよ
I saw the pitiful way you looked at me when that medicine got blown up!
てめえ　俺を哀れむような目で見ただろ
Quit worryin' about other people, ya damn wimp!
いっちょまえに他人の気遣いしてんじゃねえぞ　モヤシ野郎
ウイルスなんざ寝てりゃ　余裕で治せんだよ
This virus'll go away by itself with a good night's sleep!
寺坂…　お前…
Terasaka... You mean—
そんなくずでも　息の根止めりゃ殺人罪だ
Murder is murder, even if it's a piece of trash like that.
てめえはキレるに任せて　１００億のチャンスを手放すのか
You gonna give in to the crazy and throw your chance at ten billion out the window?
Terasaka-kun's right, Nagisa-kun.
寺坂君の言うとおりです　渚君
その男を殺しても何の価値もない
Killing him isn't worth it,
逆上しても不利になるだけです
and being in a blind rage will only work against you.
Besides, he doesn't know anything about the remedy.
そもそも　彼に治療薬に関する知識などない
下にいた毒使いの男に聞きましょう
We'll ask the poisoner downstairs.
そんな男は　気絶程度で十分です
Just knock him out. That's enough.
おいおい　余計な水差すんじゃねえよ
Hey now, quit being a wet blanket!
本気で殺しに来させなきゃ意味ねえんだ
If he doesn't come at me with true killing intent, what's the point?
このちびの本気の殺意を屈辱的に返り討ちにして
I'll use this squirt's bloodlust for revenge in a most humiliating way,
初めて俺の恥は消し去れる
and finally my own shame will disappear!
渚君　寺坂君のスタンガンを拾いなさい
Nagisa-kun, take Terasaka-kun's stun gun.
その男の命と先生の命
His life, or my life. His words, or Terasaka-kun's words.
その男の言葉と寺坂君の言葉
それぞれどちらに価値があるのか考えるんです
Think carefully, now: which are more worthy?
寺坂
Terasaka!
お前　これ熱ヤベえぞ
You... You've got one hell of a fever!
こんな状態で来てたのかよ
How'd you even make it here like this?
うるせえ…
Shaddup. You wanna look at somethin', look there.
見るなら　あっちだ
やれ　渚
Do it, Nagisa.
死なねえ範囲で…ぶっ殺せ
Kill him to within an inch of his life.
Ooh, don't you look cool!
カッコイイねえ
殺せんせー　渚　スタンガン　しまっちゃったよ
Korosensei, Nagisa's put the stun gun away!
ナイフ使う気満々だな　安心したぜ
I see you're determined to use the knife. That's a relief.
一応言っとくが
Oh, and just so you know,
ここに薬の予備がある
I do have some spare vials of that remedy.
渚君が本気で殺しに来なかったり
If you don't come at me like you mean it,
下のやつらが俺の邪魔をしようものなら
or if your pals get in our way,
こいつも破壊する
you can kiss these babies goodbye.
烏間　邪魔すんじゃねえぞ
Hear that, Karasuma? Stay out of this!
作るのに　１カ月はかかるそうだ
This stuff takes a good month to make.
人数分には足りないが　最後の希望だぜ
There's not enough for everyone, but it is your last hope.
烏間先生
Karasuma-sensei.
もし渚君が　生命の危機と判断したら
If you determine that Nagisa-kun's life is in danger,
迷わず鷹岡先生を撃ってください
please don't hesitate to shoot Takaoka-sensei.
さきざきまで見通せるこいつがここまで言うとは…
For him to say that when he can usually see what's coming...
今までになく　危険な状況ということか
This must be our most dangerous predicament yet.
いや　俺が見ても間違いなくまずい
Even I can tell that much.
３人の殺し屋たちは何とかこちらのペースに持ち込んで　倒すことができたが
We may have managed to defeat those three assassins on our own terms...
今は完全に立場が逆
but now the tables are completely turned!
潮田渚が先に暗殺に持ち込もうとしても…
Even if Shiota Nagisa did try to turn this into an assassination...
ほら　どうした
What's wrong? Aren't you going to kill me?
殺すんじゃなかったのか
今の鷹岡は前と別物だ
Takaoka's a whole different man.
He's in battle mode!
最初から戦闘モード
心が狂気で満たされても　精鋭軍人
Even with a mind gone mad, he's still an elite soldier.
His impregnable defense will shut down any surprise attack!
いかなる奇襲も通じないほど隙がない
体格
The build!
技術
The skills!
経験
The experience!
全国模試で１位を取るより　数倍至難だ
Defeating him is far harder than scoring in first place in the national mock exams.
勝負にならない
It's not even a contest.
勝てるわけねえよ　あんな化け物
There's no way he can beat that monster!
おいおい　へばるなよ　今までのは序の口だぞ
Hey, don't go getting tired on me.
We're only just getting started!
Looks like it's time for me to pull out one of these too.
さーて　そろそろ俺もこいつを使うか
A traumatic image accompanies his knife in my dreams.
ナイフと共に　夢に出てくるトラウマがある
あのとき見せたこいつの笑顔だ
When he caught me off-guard with that smile of his—
that's when everything went off the rails.
あの笑顔に虚をつかれてから　全てが狂った
もう絶対同じ過ちは繰り返さねえ
I will not make the same mistake again.
手足切り落として標本にしてやる
I'll cut off your hands and feet and have them stuffed and mounted.
ずっと手元に置いて　めでてやるよ
I'll keep them with me and cherish them forever.
烏間先生　もう撃ってください
Karasuma-sensei! You've got to shoot him!
渚　死んじゃうよ　あんなの
Nagisa's gonna die!
Wait.
待て　手出しすんじゃねえ
Stay out of it!
まだ放っとけって　寺坂
Are we still leaving them to it, Terasaka?
そろそろ俺も参戦したいんだけど
I'm just about ready to join the fray myself.
業…てめえは練習サボってばっかで知らねえだろうがよ
You been skippin' practice, Karma, so you don't know, but Nagisa...
渚のやつ
まだ何か隠し玉　持ってるようだぜ
He's still got somethin' up his sleeve.
今のが…必殺技
Was that the deadly technique?
そうだ…といっても　まるでぴんとこないだろう
Yes. But then again,
it didn't look like one, did it?
When I was in a tight spot as an assassin,
殺し屋としてピンチのとき
俺はこれを編み出すことで切り抜けた
I used this to squeeze my way out.
この技の発動には条件がある
But it has conditions that must be met—three of them.
大きく分けて　それは３つ
１つ　武器を２本持っていること
First: you must have two weapons.
２つ　敵が手だれであること
Second: you must be up against an expert.
そして３つ　敵が殺される恐怖を知っていること
And third: your foe must know the terror of being killed.
よかった
Good.
全部揃ってる
That's all of them.
何だ
What...
Takaoka-sensei...
鷹岡先生
実験台になってください
Will you be my guinea pig?
何なんだ
Wh-What are you doing?!
必殺技といっても　必ず殺す技ではない
A deadly technique doesn't necessarily kill instantly.
そもそも暗殺者なら　理想的状況なら必ず殺すのは当たり前だ
Given the ideal conditions, of course, any assassin can do the deed.
だが　現実はそううまくは運ばない
But reality is rarely that agreeable,
especially when your target is a pro with an airtight defense.
特にターゲットが隙のない手だれのときはな
だが　そんなピンチに必ず殺せる理想的状況をつくり出す技
This technique can reliably create an ideal killing situation in such a bind.
それがこの　必ず殺すための技だ
It sets the stage for an instant kill.
必ず殺す…ための
Sets the stage, huh?
Move from a standstill, as fast as you can,
ノーモーションから最速で
最も遠くで　最大に…
as far as you can, and make it as loud as possible.
くそがき
You... lousy... brat!
This works best when they're almost within range.
タイミングは　ナイフの間合いのわずか外
接近するほど敵の意識はナイフに集まる
The closer you get, the more the target will focus on your knife.
Gently let go of that knife in midair while their attention is on it, then...
その意識ごと　ナイフを空中に置くように捨て
そのまま…
な…何が起こっ…
What... just... happ—
暗殺者は　その数瞬を逃さない
An assassin...
will not overlook those few moments.
流れるように　２本目のやいばを抜くが早いか
In one fluid motion, swiftly draw your second blade, and...
嘘だ…
It... can't be...
こんながきに…二度も…
This brat... got me... again?!
とどめを刺せ　渚
Finish him off, Nagisa.
首辺りにたっぷり流しゃ　完全に気絶する
A good jolt to the neck'll knock him out cold.
殺意を教わった
He taught me bloodlust.
抱いちゃいけない種類の殺意があるってこと
That some kinds of bloodlust are wrong to hold on to,
その殺意から引き戻してくれる友達の大切さも…
and how important it is to have friends to pull you away from that.
殴られる痛みを　実戦の恐怖を
The pain of being hit, the fear of a real fight...
この人からたくさん教わった
I've learned so much from this man.
He'd done terrible things, but setting that aside,
ひどいことをした人だけど
それとは別に　授業への感謝はちゃんと言わなきゃいけないと思った
I thought I ought to thank him for his lessons.
感謝を伝えるなら…
And I figured...
やめろ
No...
そういう顔をすべきだと思ったから
...I couldn't thank him without putting on a smile.
Just, please... don't end this with that smile of yours!
その顔で終わらせるのだけはやめてくれ
もう一生　その顔が悪夢の中から離れなくなる
That face will haunt my nightmares until the day I die!
鷹岡先生
Takaoka-sensei...
ありがとうございました
Thank you.
よっしゃ～　ボス撃破
Yes!
We beat the boss!
やった
Hooray!
Not bad.
やるじゃん
You okay, Nagisa?
大丈夫か　渚
Yeah.
Well done, Nagisa-kun.
よくやってくれました　渚君
I was so worried about how things would turn out. I'm relieved.
今回ばかりはどうなるかと思いましたが　安心しました
Right. I'm fine, but... now what?
うん　僕は平気だけど
でも　どうしよう…
The remedy we took from Takaoka-sensei won't be enough.
鷹岡先生から奪った分じゃ　足りない…
Let's start by getting out of here.
とにかくここを脱出する
I've called a chopper, so you wait here.
ヘリを呼んだから　君らは待機だ
I'll bring up the poisoner.
俺が毒使いの男を連れてくる
Ha. You're not gonna need no stinkin' remedy.
てめえらに　薬なんぞ必要ねえ
You brats thought you could get out of here alive, eh?
がきども　このまま生きて帰れるとでも思ったか
We've defeated the man who hired you.
お前たちの雇い主はすでに倒した
You have no further reason to fight us, right?
戦う理由はないはずだ
I've mostly recovered, and these students are plenty strong.
俺はじゅうぶん回復した
生徒たちもじゅうぶん強い
How about we stop now before anyone else gets hurt?
これ以上　互いに被害が出ることはやめにしないか
Yeah, okay.
ああ　いいよ
You just don't know when to give up—
諦め悪い…
えっ　いいよ？
Wait, "okay"?
Our contracts don't cover avenging the boss.
ボスの敵討ちは俺らの契約には含まれてねえ
Besides, it's like I said: you don't need any remedy.
それに言ったろ　そもそもお前らに薬なんざ必要ねえって
This here's what I gave you:
お前らに盛ったのはこっち　食中毒菌を改良したものだ
a souped-up version of the common stomach bug.
It'll keep going strong for another three hours or so,
あと３時間くらいは猛威を振るうが
but then it'll rapidly lose its efficacy and become harmless.
その後　急速に活性を失って無毒になる
Now, this is what our boss told us to use.
ボスが使えと指示したのはこっちだ
If we had, you'd really be in dire straits.
これを使えば　お前ら　マジでヤバかったがな
Right before using that virus, we three talked-eth it over.
そのウイルスを使う直前に３人で話し合ったぬ
Our boss only gave-eth you one hour.
ボスの設定した時間は１時間ぬ
We figured we could do the handover without having to resort-eth to a deadly virus.
だったら　わざわざ殺すウイルスじゃなくても　取引はできるぬ
It was enough to make you feel like your lives were in danger, anyway.
お前らが命の危険を感じるには　十分だったろう
So you went against orders?
あいつの命令に逆らったってこと
Can you do that when he's paying you?
お金もらってるのに　そんなことしていいの
What are you, stupid?
アホか
If you think pros will do anything for money, you got another think comin'.
プロが何でも金で動くと思ったら　大間違いだ
We'll do our best to abide by our client's wishes, of course...
もちろん　クライアントの意に沿うように最善は尽くすが…
I'll blow this remedy up right before their eyes.
この薬はな　やつらの目の前で爆破してやる
絶望の顔が見ものだぜ
Oh, I can't wait to see their faces crushed with despair!
...but he never had any intention of giving you the remedy.
ボスははなから薬を渡すつもりはないようだった
So either we become the killers of a bunch of respectable junior-high kids,
堅気の中学生を大量に殺した実行犯になるか
or we take a hit to our professional standing.
プロとしての評価を落とすか
We just calmly weighed up which option posed a greater risk to our future.
どちらが俺らの今後にリスクが高いか　冷静にはかりに掛けただけよ
And that's why, sorry to say, none of you will be dying.
まあ　そんな訳で　お前らは残念ながら誰も死なねえ
Give the patients that supplement and put 'em to bed.
その栄養剤　患者に飲ませて寝かしてやんな
Just like it says on the tin, they'll feel even better than before they were sick.
倒れる前より元気になったって　手紙が届くほどだ
I'll believe it once I see those students home safe and sound.
信用するかは　生徒たちが回復したのを見てからだ
We'll need to detain you for a while for questioning.
事情も聴くし　しばらく拘束させてもらうぞ
Ah, well. You've got a week to wind it up before our next job starts.
まあ　しゃあねえな
来週は次の仕事　入ってるから　それ以内にな
What's this?
なーんだ
Not going-eth for a rematch, buddy?
リベンジマッチ　やらないんだ　おじさんぬ
Aren't you just thirsting for revenge?
俺のこと　殺したいほど恨んでないの
I don't kill-eth people out of spite.
俺は私怨で人を殺したことはないぬ
I'll wait for the day someone puts-eth a hit out on you.
誰かがお前を殺す依頼をよこす日を待つぬ
You'd better become-eth someone worth targeting.
だから　狙われるくらいの人物になるぬ
And there you have it, kids!
そういうこった　がきども
If you really want us to come kill you, you've gotta make it big first!
本気で殺しに来てほしかったら　偉くなれ
Then we'll give you the pro assassin's grand tour!
そんときゃ　プロの殺し屋のフルコースを教えてやるよ
The assassins were gone,
殺し屋たちは去っていった
having left us with their own words of encouragement of sorts.
彼らなりのエールを僕らに残して…
One buzz from Karasuma.
烏間からバイブ１回　脱出完了の合図ね
That's the signal that they've escaped.
Hey, I wanna go down the mountain and see the ocean.
ね～え　麓に行って海が見たいわ
Won't someone drive me down there?
誰か車で連れ出してくださらない
Me! Me me me! Pick me!
はいはいはい
And so our big infiltration mission was completed with no one at the hotel the wiser.
こうして　僕らの大規模潜入ミッションは
ホテル側の誰一人気付かないままコンプリートした
Terasaka-kun?
寺坂君
Thanks for calling me out back then.
ありがとう　あのとき声を掛けてくれて
I was about to make the wrong move.
間違えるところだった
Pfft.
One less student'd make it that much harder to kill that octopus.
一人欠けたら　タコ殺す難易度上がんだろうが
Yeah. Sorry.
うん　ごめん
We went back to our hotel, where everyone was waiting
僕らはみんなの待つホテルに戻って　もう大丈夫なことを伝えた
and told them it was going to be okay.
We slept like logs, each of us tired out in different ways,
それぞれがそれぞれの疲れで　泥のように眠って
and when we woke, it was evening on the next day.
起きたのは次の日の夕方だった
That was one crazy day.
何か　ものすごい一日だったね
I'm just glad we got through it in one piece.
ひとまず無事でよかったよ
You were the one in the most danger, you know!
渚が一番危なかったんだから
Sorry.
ごめん
You do get into sticky spots now and then.
何か時々危なっかしいよね
We worry, you know!
みんな心配してんだから
Good morning!
おはよう　って夕方だけどね
Or should I say "evening"?
Feeling better?
元気になった
Yes, thank you.
おかげさまで
I see everyone's in their P.E. gear.
やっぱみんな　ジャージーなのね
We're the only guests, and these are nice and comfy.
他に客　誰もいないし　これが楽だわ
And it'd be cruel to have to think up a whole new day's worth of outfits.
全員の私服２日分考えんのえぐ過ぎるしね
Say what?
何言ってんの
So Korosensei's in there?
今　あん中に殺せんせーいるの
Yeah. It's not like it's going to work,
駄目もとだけど　戻ったとき殺せるようにがっちり固めておくんだって
but he's in there nice and tight so we can kill him when he reverts.
Karasuma-sensei has been leading the charge without rest.
烏間先生が不眠不休で指揮執ってる
He shows no signs of fatigue at all. Pretty amazing!
疲れも見せず　すごい人だよ
He really is. I wonder if we'll be as awesome as him in ten years.
すげえよな
あと１０年で　俺たちあんな超人になれんのかな
Who knows?
さあな
Bitch-sensei might not look like it, but she's great too.
ビッチ先生も　ああ見えてすごい人だし
So were the assassins we met at the hotel.
ホテルで会った殺し屋たちもそうだった
Those moves mastered through long years of experience
長年の経験で　すごい技術身に付けていたり
Go, me.
and their work ethic really inspired me.
仕事に対して　しっかりした考えがあったり
Gimme a max potion.
Then there are people like Takaoka who I really don't want to turn into.
と思えば　鷹岡みたいにああはなりたくないってやつもいて
We follow people we admire and leave behind the ones we reject.
いいなと思った人は追い掛けて
駄目だと思ったやつは追い越して
Growing up is probably just doing that over and over again.
たぶん　それの繰り返しなんだろうな
大人になってくって
What was that explosion?!
爆発したぞ
Did we get him?!
やれたか
Even as we asked that,
とはいえ　結果はみんなうすうす分かっていて…
we already knew the answer.
You suffered so much on account of my cowardice.
先生のふがいなさから　苦労を掛けてしまいました
But you battled enemies and a virus—and did a fine job of it too.
ですが　皆さん　敵と戦い　ウイルスと戦い
本当によく頑張りました
Good morning, Korosensei.
おはようございます　殺せんせー
You're just not the same without your tentacles.
やっぱ　先生は触手がなくっちゃね
Morning!
Good morning, students.
はい　おはようございます
Now, let's enjoy the rest of our trip, shall we?
では　旅行の続きを楽しみましょうか
You bet!
はい
But we're going back tomorrow morning.
ったって　もうあしたの朝には帰るだろう
Say what?!
何言ってるんですか
With all the time I spent in my Absolute Defense Form, I've barely gotten to enjoy myself at all!
先生はほとんど完全防御形態でしたから　遊び足りませんよ
Well, you're sure full of energy.
元気だな…
This is a one-time thing: summer camp with my students!
せっかくの生徒たちとの合宿
We Love Summer!
この夏は一度きりのもの
We can't waste a single second!
一秒だって無駄にできませんよ
What are you doing?!
何するんですか
You just said not to waste a single second, right?
一秒でも無駄にしないって　言ったよね
Ah yes, Karma-kun.
さすがは業君　相手が油断している…
Wait until your target lets down his—
Hey, hey, hey!
I thought this might be our chance to do him in.
今なら殺せると思ったんだけどね
Want to take a shot, Nagisa-kun?
渚君も撃つ
We've got to make the most of the time we have!
そうね　時間いっぱい楽しまないと
I'm all for that!
大賛成
Here goes!
いくよ
Wait up!
待ってよ
Over here!
Since I'm feeling better and all...
せっかく元気になったから
You put on a swimsuit underneath?
下着着てたんだ
Well, I didn't!
私　着てない
Ha!
そーれ
Now you've done it!
やったな
もませろ
Lemme at 'em!
Hooray!
わい　先生も交ぜてください
Me too, me too!
Sure!
いいよ
Wait, I'm just going to swell right up, aren't I?!
よく考えたら　ふやけてしまうじゃないですか
Tch!
He realized.
気付かれたか
That's right. This is it!
そうだよ　これだよ
This is what summer's all about!
夏のイベントはこうでなくっちゃ
Hey, me too!
俺も交ぜて
Let me—
Die!
死ね
Bit on the small side, huh?
ちっさ
Now, students, there'll be fireworks after this!
皆さん　この後は　花火ですからね
Don't forget to play with me too!
ちゃんと先生とも遊んでくださいね
That octopus...
あのタコ
Karasuma-san, should we start heading out?
烏間さん　われわれは撤収した方がいいですかね
Yes, please do.
ああ　そうしてくれ
Hang on!
ちょっと
I thought you were busy burying him in concrete!
コンクリート作業してるんじゃなかったの
You should've invited me if you were heading to the beach!
海で遊ぶんなら　誘いなさいよ
What a swimsuit!
何て水着だ
What desperation.
必死過ぎ
Shut it, you brats!
黙れ　がきども
Hey, Karasuma, what do you say?
ああ　烏間　どう　今から
Let's leave these kids behind and check out that—
こんながきども放っておいて　あっちの入り江を…
どうでもいい
Whatever.
You really are a bitch.
やっぱり　ビッチですね
What was that?!
何ですって
You squirts have been giving some real cheek lately!
最近　ますます生意気なのよ　あんたたち
Don't you mess with me, brats!
ナメてんじゃないわよ　がきども
待て
You did well.
頑張りましたね
Our E Class—the End Class—is the assassination classroom.
エンドのＥ組は暗殺教室
We are killers,
僕らは殺し屋
and our target is our teacher.
ターゲットは…
先生
Good morning, students.
皆さん　おはようございます
Time for a second term full of hard work in studying and assassination alike!
２学期も　勉強に暗殺に大いに励みましょう
And in this assassination classroom we share with Korosensei...
殺せんせーと僕らの暗殺教室
the bell signals the start of another school day.
始業のベルは　今日も鳴る
太陽が射す　閉ざした瞼の裏側に赤い残像
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
革の鞄に　ノートとペンを　さあ歩き出そう
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
描いても描いても　綺麗にならない
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
選んだ絵の具に　罪はない
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
昨日の夜中に見た流れ星　まだ覚えている
I was waiting for…
I was waiting for...
Hello shooting-star Hello shooting-star again
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
待っていたよ
夢を見るあの子はずっと
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
ここにいるの　Ah　Ah
Is always here
koko ni iru no
あの日のまま　Ah　Ah
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
また光って
Shine again
mata hikatte